Guide to the Public Art Fund Archive 1966-2009 MSS.270
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: City Walls, 174151
  - Subseries I.B: Artist Files, 179133
    - City scenes/National Paint - bicentennial project, 3 of 3, 1976; 180879 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - City scenes/unrealized - Houston, 1976; 180880 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - City scenes/unrealized - Washington D.C., 1976; 180881 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Bearden, Romare/City Scenes/Atlanta, Georgia, 1976; 180882 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Flavin, Dan/Two hundred years of American art - Whitney Museum, 1976; 180883 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Haas, Richard, 1976; 180884 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Hartnett, Elaine, 1976; 180885 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Henderson, Jean/City Scenes/Louisville, Kentucky, 1976; 180886 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Janney, Christopher, undated; 196883 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Kepets, Hugh, 1976; 180887 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Little Italy Walls - Haas, Richard & Stern, Marina, 1976; 180888; Photographs (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Mead, George/City Scenes - Oakland, California, 1976; 180889 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Propp, Marilyn/City Scenes - Kansas City, MO, 1976; 180890 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Fishbone, Bob & Lindquist, Sarah, 1976-1977; 180950 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Haas, Richard/City Scenes - Boston, Massachusetts, 1 of 2, 1976-1977; 180951 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Haas, Richard/City Scenes - Boston, Massachusetts, 1 of 2, 1976-1977; 180952 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Haas, Richard - "City Walls" - Restoration, 1980; 200973 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Mailman, Cynthia, 1977; 180953 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Wirsum, Karl, 1976-1977; 180954 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Durst, Seymour, 1976-1977; 180955 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Farris, Ron "Kip" & Farley, Richard/City Scenes - Denver, Colorado, 1976-1977; 180956 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Sonfist, Alan, 1978; 180957 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Crum, Jason - mural restoration, 1979-1981; 180958 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Milicevic, Tania - Repainting, 1981-1982; 180959 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Subseries I.C: Publications, 180969
    This series includes brochures, publications, and magazine articles collected and compiled by City Walls.
    - Street art N.Y.: a photo essay, 1968; 180970 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Neighborhood Street Festivals New York City, 1969; 180971 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - The Art Gallery Magazine, 1970; 180972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Using Walls (Outdoors), 1970; 180973 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - City Walls Publications, 1970-1974; 180974 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Jersey City Awake, 1973; 180975 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Environmental Communications, 1974-1979; 180976 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - New York City Cultural Council ("To be a creator..." brochure), undated; 181022 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Series II: Public Arts Council, 174154
  Arranged chronologically, this series documents projects that were initiated by the Public Arts Council of the Municipal Arts Society. Significant gaps exist and the materials are not a comprehensive reflection of all projects completed during the time period. The series is divided into six subseries.
  - Subseries II.A: General Organizational Files, 179138
    - Public Arts Council Statements & History, 1970-1976; 181037 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Public Arts Council advisory board & other correspondence, 1973-1978; 181038 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Public Space/Public sculpture commissioning program, 1974-1976; 181039 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Unrealized project - Waterside Plaza floor printing, 1975; 181040 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Public Arts Council bank account closed, 1976; 181041 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Midtown Arts Advisory Committee, 1977; 180085 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Press releases, 1978; 180087 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Art Commission of New York, 1973-1974; 180084 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - "The Great American Quilt" - A design for the unveiling of the stature of liberty for its rededication, 1984-1986; 180086 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Subseries II.B: Public Art Council Projects, 179135
    - Index of public art in New York City - Research (1 of 2), 1971-1973; 181046 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Index of public art in New York City (2 of 2), undated; 181047 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Walk Through Sculpture in the Park, 1974; 181048 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Walking Tour Guide of Lower Manhattan (1 of 3), 1975; 181049 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Walking Tour Guide of Lower Manhattan (2 of 3), 1975; 181050 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Walking Tour Guide of Lower Manhattan (3 of 3), 1975; 181051 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Platforms for Design (1 of 4), 1976; 181052 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Platforms for Design (2 of 4), 1975-1976; 181053 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Platforms for Design (3 of 4), 1974-1977; 181054; Press (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Platforms for Design (4 of 4), 1976; 181055; Images (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Subseries II.C: Artist Projects, 1971-1977; 179136
    - King, William, 1971; 181056 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Gourfain, Peter, 1972; 181057 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Oppenheim, Dennis, 1972; 181058 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Slivka, David, 1974; 181059 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Snelson, Kenneth - 1 of 2, 1974; 181060 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Snelson, Kenneth - 2 of 2, 1974; 181061; Images (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Hamner, Richard - unrealized, 1975; 181062 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Tumarkin, Igael, 1975; 181063 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Von Ringelheim, Paul, 1975; 181064 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - di Suvero, Mark - 1 of 4, 1975; 181065 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - di Suvero, Mark - 2 of 4, 1975; 181066 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - di Suvero, Mark - 3 of 4, 1975; 181067 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - di Suvero, Mark - 4 of 4, 1975; 181068 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Canole, 1976; 181069 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Milkowski, Antoni - unrealized project, 1976; 181070 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Negrin, Lee, 1976; 181071 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Tumarkin, Igael - 1 of 2, 1976; 181072 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Tumarkin, Igael - 2 of 2, 1976; 181073 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Valinski, Dennis - 1 of 3, 1976; 181074 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Valinski, Dennis - 2 of 3, 1976; 181075 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Valinski, Dennis - 3 of 3, 1976; 181076 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - King, William - 1 of 3, 1976; 181077 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - King, William - 2 of 3, 1976; 181078 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - King, William - 3 of 3, 1976; 181079 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Indiana, Robert, 1977-1978; 190518 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Subseries II.D: Community Environmental Sculpture Program, 179137
    - General artist correspondence and planning (1 of 5), 1967; 181080 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - General artist correspondence and planning (2 of 5), 1967; 181081 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - General artist correspondence and planning (3 of 5), 1967; 181082 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - General artist correspondence and planning (4 of 5), 1967-1972; 181084 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - General artist correspondence and planning (5 of 5), 1967-1972; 181085 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Ramirez, Edmundo, 1972; 181086 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Meadmore, Clement - "Split Ring", 1972-1973; 181087 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Meadmore, Clement - "Swing", 1972-1987; 181088 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Doyle, Tom, 1973-1974; 181089 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Lockpez, Inverna, 1974; 181090 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Fugate-Wilcox, Terry, 1974-1987; 181091 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Photographs, undated; 181092 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Subseries II.E: Consulting projects, 181158
    - Borough Hall Sculpture Garden - Brooklyn, 1971-1976; 181159 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - College Art Association Meeting, 1974-1975; 181160 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Consulting Central Park Restoration / Grand Central Station Concert, 1977; 181161 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Consulting for Fox Square / Plaza, 1973-1974; 181162 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Consulting Plaza Sites for Sculpture, 1975-1976; 181163 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Consulting Queens Court House, 1976; 181164 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Creative Time Project – Crafts in Action, 1974; 181165 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Creative Time Project – Sail, 1974; 181166 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Louise Nevelson Plaza, 1976-1979; 181167 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - "In the Event of Living Sculpture" Benefit - Phyllis Yampovsky, 1978; 181168 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - New York City Commission on Cultural Affairs, 1974-1975; 181169 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - New York Cultural Center, 1972; 181170 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Subseries II.F: Slides and Negatives, 1971-1978; 181083
    - Cooper-Hewitt Sculpture Symposium/Pavia, Philip/Three untitled works, 1971; 181093 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Cooper-Hewitt Sculpture Symposium/Pavia, Philip/Wind, Sand, and Stars, 1971-1972; 181094 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - King, William/Exhibition of five sculptures/Borough Hall, Brooklyn, 1971-1972; 181095 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Community Environmental Sculpture.../Lockpez, Inverna/Walking Pineapples, 1972; 181096 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Community Environmental Sculpture.../Meadmore, Clement/Split Ring and Swing, 1972-1973; 181097 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Community Environmental Sculpture.../Ramirez, Eduardo/Columnade, 1972; 181099 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Walk Through: Sculpture in the Park, 1972; 181098 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Snelson, Kenneth/Exhibition of five sculptures/Waterside Plaza, 1976; 181100 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Commissions for Public Spaces/King, William-Up/Tacha, Athena-Tide Park, 1975-1978; 181101 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Canole/Accents on Nature, 1976; 181102 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Valinski, Dennis/Exhibitions of three sculptures/Waterside Plaza, 1976; 181103 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Platforms for Design, 1977; 181104 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Tumarkin, Igael, undated; 181105 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Times Square Site Photos, undated; 181106 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Messages to the Public Negatives, undated; 202002 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - General - Negatives, undated; 181107 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Series III: Percent for Art, 179127
  Materials in this series document the formation of New York City's Percent for Art program. This includes drafts of legislation, rules and procedures, budget documents, general correspondence with the Department of Cultural Affairs, and research material on nation-wide Percent for Art programs.
  The series is divided into four subseries.
  - Subseries III.A: Lobbying and Legislation, 179128
    Arranged chronologically, the folders in this series include information on federal, state, and city legislation, consisting of proposals and drafts of legislation, senate reports, congressional records, and art and architecture hearing documentation. There is also research on out of state legislation and correspondence from out of state representatives. Materials include a list of committee members who helped start the project in New York, budget and contract drafts, correspondence with Doris Freedman, the National Endowment the Arts, the House of Representatives and a White House letter from Richard Nixon.
    - Federal Legislation and Drafts, 1967-1979; 181114 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - New York City Legislation and Drafts (1 of 2), 1965-1982; 181115 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - New York State Legislation and Drafts (2 of 2), 1968-1979; 181116 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - AD HOC Committee Members, 1972-1979; 181117 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Public Arts Council: Lobby for Federal Legislation, 1973-1974; 181118 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Out of State Legislation, 1974-1979; 181119 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Public Arts Council: Lobbying for City Legislation (1 of 4), 1974-1975; 181120 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Public Arts Council: Lobbying for City Legislation (2 of 4), 1976-1979; 181121 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Public Arts Council: Lobbying for City Legislation (3 of 4), 1976-1979; 181122 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Public Arts Council: Lobbying for City Legislation (4 of 4), 1979-1981; 181123 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Public Art Fund: Lobbying and Passage of Legislation, 1981-1982; 181124 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Bank Forms and Budgets, 1982-1986; 181125 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Sample contracts, undated; 181126 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Subseries III.B: Project Planning, 1983-1994; 1983-1986; 179129
    Arranged chronologically, materials in this series documents Percent for Art activity from 1983-1986.This includes general correspondence with the Department of Cultural Affairs, information about the current state of the program, procedures, rules and regulations, and research material on nation-wide Percent for Art programs. Much of the correspondence is between Susan K. Freedman and The Department of Cultural Affairs, including meeting agendas, implementation procedures, and information on the East Harlem Art-park project. The series also includes folders from research the Public Art Fund conducted in 1994, regarding procedures for de-accessioning public artwork.
    - General Correspondence (January-May), 1983; 181127 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence (June-December), 1983; 181128 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Rules and Procedures, 1983; 181129 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Press Clippings, 1983-1986; 181130 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence (1 of 2), 1984; 181131 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence (2 of 2), 1984; 181132 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Panelist Surveys, 1984; 181133 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - North Hills Library, 1984; 181134 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Board of Education, 1984-1985; 181135 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Panelists, 1984-1986; 181136 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Project Listings, 1984-1986; 181137 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence (1 of 2), 1985; 181138 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - General Correspondence (2 of 2), 1986; 181139 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Draft of Contract (Department of Cultural Affairs), 1986; 181140 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Deaccessioning Research, 1 of 2, 1994; 181156 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Deaccessioning Research, 2 of 2, 1994; 181157 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Subseries III.C: General Administrative Files, 181141
    - Percent legislation in other states, 1976; 181142 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - William S. Allison-subway consulting fee, 1977-1978; 181143 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Kent Barwick-subway consulting fee, 1978; 181144 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - General statements on public art, 1978; 181145 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Arthur Ross, 1978-1979; 181146 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - 1979 Brochure, 181147 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Co-op City-sculpture exhibition, 1979; 181148 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Percent guidelines in other states, 1983; 181149 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Delmar vs. muralist, 1984; 181150 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Public art symposium at Edith C. Blum-Art Institute at Bard College, 1984; 181151 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Proposals-MTA Art Panel, 1984; 181152 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - East Harlem Art Park, 1984; 181153 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Percent for Art Panel-meeting notes, 1984-1985; 181154 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Year-end reports 1984-1986, 181155 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Public art preservation committee symposium, October 17, 1980; 181171 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Lecture, Canada-Jenny Dixon, 1981; 181172 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Percent for art exhibition pamphlets-Villard Houses, 1981; 181173 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Percent for Art-materials for catalogue-Urban Center, 1981; 181174 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Percent exhibition tour of New York state, 1981; 181175 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Guest list exhibition and reception, November 17, 1981; 181176 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Percent for Art in Architecture reception- Brooklyn Educational and Cultural Alliance, November 17, 1981; 181177 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Percent legislation exhibition, 1981; 181178 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Urban Center correspondence, June, 1981; 181179 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - White Street detention center, 1985; 181180 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Police precincts, 1985; 181181 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Brooklyn Central Library-Percent for Art panel meeting notes, 1985; 181182 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Percent Programs in other states-Prisons, 1986; 263541 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - City gallery: January-March, 1988; 181183 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Letter Response for "1%" Legislation - Federal (Art Commission), 1980; 201974 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Percent for Art Exhibition 1980, 201975 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Percent for Art-Exhibition at Urban Center, 1981; 202024 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Percent for Art Show (City Gallery), 1988; 201976 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - National Percent for Art Newsletter, undated; 201977 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Percent for Art - Slide Registry - Forms and general Information, undated; 201978 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Percent - current projects, undated; 201979 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Subseries III.D: Percent for Art nation-wide research file, 181213
    - Research Materials, 1974-1978; 181214 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Alabama-Nebraska, 1972-1978; 181215 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Nevada-Vermont, 1972-1978; 181216 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Virginia-Denmark, 1972-1978; 181217 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Catalog forms, undated; 181218 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Percent for Art plans and proposals, undated; 196879 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Series IV: Director's Files, 201882
  This series consists of documents created by directors who have worked with the Public Art Fund throughout its 30-year history. Arrangement closely resembles the original order of the folders. This series is divided into four subseries.
  - Subseries IV.A: Doris Freedman Papers, 1968-1981; 181108
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, 1968-1971; 181231 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Cultural Affairs Task Force, 1 of 3, 1977; 181232 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Cultural Affairs Task Force, 2 of 3, 1977; 181233 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Cultural Affairs Task Force, 3 of 3, 1977; 181234 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Consulting, 1971-1974, 181235 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Public Sculpture, undated; 181236 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Juror/consultant for Brad Goldberg of Rhode Island School of Design, 1978; 181237; Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Kreisler Borg Florman-sculpture purchase-Harlem, 1970-1975; 181238 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Community Council/Parks & Recreation, 1973; 181541 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - President of Municipal Art Society, 1 of 4, 1978-1979; 181239 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - President of Municipal Art Society, 2 of 4, 1978-1979; 181240 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - President of Municipal Art Society, 3 of 4, 1978-1979; 181241 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - President of Municipal Art Society, 4 of 4, 1978-1979; 181242 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Municipal Art Society-1979 awards, 181243 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Biographies/resumes, 1969-1978; 181244 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Awards received, undated; 181245 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Albright college, 1968; 181246 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Essays in The Livable City, 1974-1982; 181247 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Essays 1969-1975, 181248 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - North Jersey Cultural Council, 1974; 181249 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Transcript of panel discussion at Lehman college, 1971; 181250 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Institute of Texan cultures-speaker, 1977; 181251 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Obituaries/Condolence notes, 1979-1982; 181252 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Transcript for Doris C. Freedman film, undated; 181253 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Women in the Arts conference, 1973; 181254 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Doris C. Freedman Plaza, 1989-1992; 181255 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Notes for book, 1 of 2, 1967; 181256 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Notes for book, 2 of 2, 1967; 181257 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Art Auction, 1966; 181258 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Art Auction - mailings, 1966; 181260 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - American Jewish Congress, 1971; 181259 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Barbara Rose-New York magazine, 1970; 181261 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - General, 1969; 181262; managerial assignment questionnaire operations research council transcript (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Hannelore Hahn/Minnesota, Ft Worth, Missouri/Outdoor sculpture directory research, 1969-1970; 181263 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Hannelore Hahn/Oregon, Sarasota, Georgia/Outdoor sculpture directory research, 1969-1970; 181264 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Hannelore Hahn/North Carolina, Philadelphia/Outdoor sculpture directory research, 1969-1970; 181278 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Artists for CORE newspapers, 1965; 181273 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Artists for CORE paperwork, 1965-1966; 181265 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Artists for CORE-invitations, posters, patron books, 1965; 181266 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Artists for CORE-photographs, 1965; 181267 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs - Annual reports 1968-1970, 181272 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs - photographs, 1969; 181277; photographs (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs - proposals, 1969; 181279 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Cultural Council Foundation-executive order, 1968-1970; 181280 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs/Cultural Council Foundation, 1 of 2, 1969-1970; 181281 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs/Cultural Council Foundation, 2 of 2, 1970-1971; 181282 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors and advisory board-Public Art Fund, 1969-1988; 181283 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper articles 1967-1970, 181276 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Jewish Communal Fund, 1 of 2, 1973-1979; 184675 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Jewish Communal Fund, 2 of 2, 1973-1979; 184676 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Philanthropy (other), 1972-1978; 184677 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Freedman, Doris - Binder - 1 of 4, 1973; 196209 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Freedman, Doris - Binder - 2 of 4/ "PERCA" Correspondence, 1973; 196210 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Freedman, Doris - Binder - 3 of 4/ Parks, Environment, Recreation and Cultural Affairs / Committee Meeting Minutes, 1973; 196211 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Freedman, Doris - Binder - 4 of 4/ "Master Plan and "By Laws", 1973; 196212 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Artists Housing (DUMBO), 1971-1972; 181288 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Artist Housing-sports complex, 1972; 181289 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Artist Housing-press clippings, 1980; 181290 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Artist Housing-correspondence, 1971; 181291 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Artist Housing-certification, 1972; 181292 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Artist Housing-correspondence, 1970; 181293 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Artist Housing-Public hearing, September 23, 1970; 181294 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Artist Housing material, 1971; 181295 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Doris C. Freedman Plaza, 1982; 181296 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Sculpture in Environment, 1967; 181297 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Invitations and exhibition pamphlets, undated; 181274 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Speeches, undated; 181275 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Random Excerpts from a descriptive, Historical, biographical Catalogue of works of Art in Public View in Manhattan, undated; 201812 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Parks Council Minutes, 1970-1975; 201886 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Parks Council / Tavern-on-the-green, 1974; 201887 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Parks Council Fall Benefit, 1976; 201888 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Search Committee - Parks Council, [1972-1974]; 201889 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Parks white papers and studies - 1 of 2, undated; 201890 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Parks white papers and studies - 2 of 2, undated; 201891 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Parks Council: Awards - 1974 / Bike Patrol, Membership and Development, c.1974; 201893 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Parks Council: Correspondence, undated; 201894 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Parks Council 1976-1979, 201895 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Parks Council 1971-1974 - 1 of 2, 201896 (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Parks Council 1971-1974 - 2 of 2, 201901 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Central Park Council, 1974; 201903 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, 1976-1977; 201904 (Box 123, Folder 12)